Guide to the Yale Summer Cabaret Scripts and Ephemera Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- 2014 Addition, 1974-2014
  - Posters, 1975-2014
    - 1994 show poster for Other Places, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1994 show poster for Endgame, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1994 show poster for Get It While You Can, 4 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1999 season poster, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1999 show poster for Maggie Cassidy, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1999 show poster for The Turn of the Screw, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 1999 show poster for A Bob Called Hope, 2 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2001 season poster, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2003 season poster, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2003 show poster for The Ten Thousand Things, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2003 show poster for Leah's Train, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2004 season poster, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2005 season poster, 2 (Box 10, Folder 148)
      Includes one copy signed by the YSC company.
    - 2006 season poster, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2011 show poster for The Tempest, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2011 show poster for As You Like It, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2011 show poster for Rose Mark'd Queen, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2012 show poster for The K of D, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2012 show poster for Of Ogres Retold, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2012 show poster for The Secret in the Wings, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2013 show poster for Tartuffe, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2013 show poster for Miss Julie, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2013 show poster for The Shoemaker's Prodigious Wife, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2013 show poster for In the Bar of a Tokyo Hotel, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2013 show poster for Hearts Desire and Drunk Enough to Say I Love You, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2014 season poster, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2014 show poster for Why Torture Is Wrong, And The People Who Love Them, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2014 show poster for A Map of Virtue, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2014 show poster for We Are Proud To Present A Presentation About The Herero Of Namibia, Formerly Known As Southwest Africa, From The German Sudwestafrika, Between The Years 1884 – 1915, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2014 show poster for Middletown, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - 2014 show poster for Summer Shorts, 1 (Box 10, Folder 148)
- 2015 Addition, 32
  - 2015 Posters and Programs (Box 10, Folder 148)
- 2016 Addition, Yale University. Summer Cabaret; 15; includes 5 programs and 9 posters, plus 1 inventory
- 2017 Addition, 2016; Yale University. Summer Cabaret; 15; includes 5 programs and 9 posters, plus 1 inventory (Box 9–10)
  - 2016 Season Programs, 6 (Box 9, Folder 149)
    5 programs and 1 inventory.
  - 2016 Posters, 9 (Box 10, Folder 148)